<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="pollutants_names">
        <item>SO2</item>
        <item>CO</item>
        <item>NO</item>
        <item>NO2</item>
        <item>O3</item>
        <item>PM2,5</item>
        <item>PM10</item>
        <item>TOL</item>
        <item>BEN</item>
        <item>XIL</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pollutants_descriptions">
        <item>Sulfur dioxide is an oxide with the molecular formula SO2. It is a colorless gas with a characteristic odor suffocating. It is released in many combustion processes as fuels like coal, oil, diesel or natural gas contain certain amounts of sulfur compounds.</item>
        <item>Carbon monoxide, with the chemical formula CO, is an odorless, colorless, flammable and highly toxic gas. It is produced by the incomplete combustion of substances such as gas, gasoline, kerosene, coal, oil, or wood snuff.</item>
        <item>Nitrogen monoxide NO is a colorless and poorly soluble in water, considered toxic. It is spread through the air produced by the combustion of automobiles and power plants.</item>
        <item>NO2 Nitrogen dioxide is one of the main pollutants from the various nitrogen oxides. Nitrogen dioxide is brown-yellowish color. It is formed as a byproduct in the process of combustion at high temperatures, such as motor vehicles and power plants.</item>
        <item>Tropospheric O3 Ozone is a colorless gas that is created through photochemical reactions between nitrogen oxides (NOx) and volatile organic compounds (VOCs) derived from sources such as burning fuel. It is the compound highlight of photochemical oxidants and is part of smog.</item>
        <item>Called PM10 and PM2.5, small solid or liquid particles of dust, ashes, soot, metal particles, cement or pollen dispersed in the atmosphere, and whose diameter is smaller than 10 .mu.m and 2.5 .mu.m, respectively. They are mainly organic material formed by inorganic compounds such as silicates and aluminates, including heavy metals and particles associated with carbon.</item>
        <item>Called PM10 and PM2.5, small solid or liquid particles of dust, ashes, soot, metal particles, cement or pollen dispersed in the atmosphere, and whose diameter is smaller than 10 .mu.m and 2.5 .mu.m, respectively. They are mainly organic material formed by inorganic compounds such as silicates and aluminates, including heavy metals and particles associated with carbon.</item>
        <item>The C6H5CH3 Toluene is a hydrocarbon added to fuels as antiknock and as a solvent for paints, coatings, rubber, resins, thinner in nitrocellulose lacquers and adhesives.</item>
        <item>The C6H6 Benzene is a colorless and highly flammable liquid with a sweet smell also carcinogenicity. It is one of the highest volume produced chemicals. Benzene is used as a starting point for other chemicals used in the manufacture of plastics, resins, nylon and synthetic fibers such as the Kevlar and certain polymers. Benzene is also used to make some types of rubbers, lubricants, dyes, detergents, drugs and pesticides.</item>
        <item>C6H4 Xylene is a colorless, flammable liquid used in the combustion of gasoline and also as an industrial solvent.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pollutants_effects">
        <item>Sulfur dioxide is an irritating and toxic gas, is the main cause of acid rain in the atmosphere and is transformed into sulfuric acid. It mainly affects the mucus and the lungs causing coughing. While this is mainly absorbed by the nasal system, exposure to high concentrations for short periods of time can irritate the respiratory tract, cause bronchitis and congested bronchial tubes of asthmatics.</item>
        <item>Carbon monoxide is a toxic gas. When it is breathed in high levels can cause physiological and pathological changes, and even death, by depriving tissues of oxygen needed for normal body functioning.</item>
        <item>This gas in the air can become nitric acid thereby producing acid rain. It causes photochemical smog covering polluted cities and adversely affects the ozone layer.</item>
        <item>Is a toxic gas, irritating and precursor of the formation of nitrate particles gas. These lead to the production of acid and high levels of PM2.5 in the air. Mainly affects the respiratory system. The short-term exposure to high levels causes damage to lung cells, while the longer-term exposure to low levels of nitrogen dioxide can cause irreversible changes in the lung tissue similar to emphysema.</item>
        <item>Its main feature is that it is a very strong oxidant with important implications for human health. The first symptoms are cough, headache, nausea, chest pain, and feeling of suffocation. Very high concentrations can damage lung function</item>
        <item>When inhaled they easily penetrate the human respiratory system, causing adverse health of people numerous respiratory diseases, cardiovascular problems, lung cancer and being behind effects. In the long term it is estimated that exposure to particulate matter may reduce life expectancy from several months to two years.</item>
        <item>When inhaled they easily penetrate the human respiratory system, causing adverse health of people numerous respiratory diseases, cardiovascular problems, lung cancer and being behind effects. In the long term it is estimated that exposure to particulate matter may reduce life expectancy from several months to two years.</item>
        <item>Can affect the nervous system, low or moderate levels can cause fatigue, confusion, weakness, memory loss, nausea, loss of appetite, loss of hearing and sight. It can also cause unconsciousness and, in extreme cases, death. These symptoms usually disappear when exposure stops.</item>
        <item>Breathing very high levels of benzene can result in death, while low levels can cause drowsiness, dizziness and accelerated heartbeat or tachycardia. Eating or drinking high levels of benzene can cause vomiting, stomach irritation, dizziness, drowsiness or seizures, and ultimately death.</item>
        <item>Its vapors can cause headache, nausea and malaise. As the benzene it is also a narcotic agent. Prolonged exposures to this product may cause changes in the central nervous system</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="array_zone_1">
        <item>Plaza de España</item>
        <item>Escuela Aguirre</item>
        <item>Avenida Ramón y Cajal</item>
        <item>Arturo Soria</item>
        <item>Villaverde</item>
        <item>Farolillo</item>
        <item>Casa de Campo</item>
        <item>Barajas Pueblo</item>
        <item>Plaza del Carmen</item>
        <item>Moratalaz</item>
        <item>Cuatro Caminos</item>
        <item>Barrio del Pilar</item>
        <item>Puente de Vallecas</item>
        <item>Méndez Álvaro</item>
        <item>Castellana</item>
        <item>Parque del Retiro</item>
        <item>Plaza de Castilla</item>
        <item>Ensanche de Vallecas</item>
        <item>Urbanización Embajada</item>
        <item>Plaza de Fernández Ladreda</item>
        <item>Sanchinarro</item>
        <item>El Pardo</item>
        <item>Juan Carlos I</item>
        <item>Tres Olivos</item>
        <item>Media Red</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="array_zone_1_json_names">
        <item>PLAZA ESPAÑA</item>
        <item>ESCUELAS AGUIRRE</item>
        <item>AVDA. RAMON Y CAJAL</item>
        <item>ARTURO SORIA</item>
        <item>VILLAVERDE</item>
        <item>FAROLILLO</item>
        <item>CASA DE CAMPO</item>
        <item>BARAJAS PUEBLO</item>
        <item>PLAZA DEL CARMEN</item>
        <item>MORATALAZ</item>
        <item>CUATRO CAMINOS</item>
        <item>BARRIO DEL PILAR</item>
        <item>PUENTE DE VALLECAS</item>
        <item>MENDEZ ALVARO</item>
        <item>CASTELLANA</item>
        <item>RETIRO</item>
        <item>PLAZA DE CASTILLA</item>
        <item>ENSANCHE DE VALLECAS</item>
        <item>URBANIZACION EMBAJADA</item>
        <item>FERNANDEZ LADREDA</item>
        <item>SANCHINARRO</item>
        <item>EL PARDO</item>
        <item>JUAN CARLOS I</item>
        <item>TRES OLIVOS</item>
        <item>MEDIA RED</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="array_LatLng_zone_1">
        <item>40.42361111,-3.712222222</item>
        <item>40.42138889,-3.682222222</item>
        <item>40.45138889,-3.677222222</item>
        <item>40.44000000,-3.639166667</item>
        <item>40.34694444,-3.713055556</item>
        <item>40.39472222,-3.731666667</item>
        <item>40.41916667,-3.747222222</item>
        <item>40.47666667,-3.580000000</item>
        <item>40.41916667,-3.703055556</item>
        <item>40.40777778,-3.645277778</item>
        <item>40.44527778,-3.706944444</item>
        <item>40.47805556,-3.711388889</item>
        <item>40.38805556,-3.651388889</item>
        <item>40.39805556,-3.686666667</item>
        <item>40.43972222,-3.690277778</item>
        <item>40.41444444,-3.682500000</item>
        <item>40.46555556,-3.688611111</item>
        <item>40.37277778,-3.611944444</item>
        <item>40.46250000,-3.580555556</item>
        <item>40.38472222,-3.718611111</item>
        <item>40.49416667,-3.660277778</item>
        <item>40.51805556,-3.774444444</item>
        <item>40.46500000,-3.608888889</item>
        <item>40.50055556,-3.689722222</item>
        <item>40.41694400,-3.703611000</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>